We created a co-pilot feature for our
app prime time. It completes the time
sheets for users using data from the
Microsoft graph such as emails, teams
calls, calendar appointments, to-dos,
etc. And it suggests time sheet entries
that will complete your time sheet and
the gaps that are in it.
So you open a time sheet and from the
time sheet, you can open a calendar
view. The calendar view shows the
completed time sheet, but we can see
there are some gaps in here. You can use
the co-pilot feature to suggest time
sheet entries that will fill in those
gaps. The time sheet entries will be
generated based on data pulled from the
Microsoft graph such as calendar
appointments, teams, calls, to-dos,
emails, etc. You'll get a proposal and
you can decide to keep it or discard it.
Then you can look at the entries
generated and you can see some
additional information with an
explanation of why that was suggested.
You can then review and adjust and in
the end you can submit your time sheet.
[Music]